This has to be one of the best bowls of
noodles you can get in Kyoto.
Hidden behind a modest wooden door
[music] with almost no signage is a
ramen shop that feels like a true local
hidden gem. Ordering is surprisingly
simple. Just use a tablet, choose what
you want, and pay. You then step out
into a small courtyard to wait for your
turn since there are only about 10
counter seats.
The shop specializes in mozzu, serving
awful [music] based ramen and skimen,
both made with springy noodles infused
with yuzu for a light citrus kick. The
ramen has a rich, deeply savory broth
with plenty of death. The Matsu skimen
is even more intense with a thicker
dipping broth that almost coats the
noodles like a sauce. My favorite of the
two.
Overall, it's hard to find many ramen
spots that serve a better bowl of
noodles than this. So, if you're in
Kyoto, make sure this spot is [music] on
your list.